Muhammad Dzaki Izza Romadhon

Jakarta 12630 | https://https://www.linkedin.com/in/dzaki-izza | 081210901616 | dzakiizza02@gmail.com Portfolio: https://dzakiizza-portfolio-app.vercel.app

SUMMARY

Highly passionate and interest in technology. Experienced in software development process from the concept or problem statement through development and deliver the end product as solution. Capable to work effectively with a different roles and team in dynamic environment. An eager learner who dedicated to improve and maintain tools, also learn new things to maximise productivity so that could get a better result or performance of product.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Frontend Engineer (Full Time Employee)

PT Feedloop Global Teknologi

- Developed a frontend of AI based application and make sure the experience matches the product design.
- Enhanced and maintained a frontend low-code software development platform on application builder.
- Created a well formatted modular code, perform testing and debugging of application.
- Collaborated with designers, backend engineers, and project manager to implement user friendly and responsive web interfaces.

UI/UX Designer (Internship)

(February 2021 – December 2021)

(September 2022 – November 2023)

Apple Developer Academy @BINUS

- Gathered business requirements and problem statements through qualitative and quantitative R&D such as interviews, desk research, and surveys to improve the product quality.
- Constructed multiple solution concepts based on User Personas, Customer Journey Maps, and SCAMPER ideation techniques.
- Ensured the solution concepts are positioned around the customer values and needs by modelling a Value Proposition Canvas and constructing a Competitive Analysis Matrix.
- Designed application interfaces start from wireframe, low to high fidelity prototype design based on Human Interface Guidelines and UI style guide for iOS app using Figma App.
- Practiced and implemented multiple development processes including Scrum, Agile, Design Thinking, and business application analysis.
- Coordinated with an ever-changing team of 5-6 members.

PROJECTS

• Feedloop AI (https://platform.feedloop.ai)

A web application that helps to craft and manage tailored AI Co-Pilots, uniquely designed to streamline a specific business process.

• Buatin App (https://buatin.app)

A standalone web application that's act as landing page to help you build an application using low code platform.

• Anime App (https://anime-app-nu.vercel.app)

A web application to showing list of anime and maintain a collection of preferred anime.

Admin App (https://admin-app-rho-one.vercel.app)

A web application to manage products that has been added and view items that are in the shopping cart.

EDUCATION

Bina Nusantara University – Jakarta, Indonesia

(September 2018 – February 2022)

Bachelor of Information Systems – Major in Business Intelligence

GPA 3.62 / 4.00

Relevant Coursework: Introduction to Programming, Database Systems, Information Systems Analysis and Design, Business Application Development, Information Systems Project Management, Data Visualization, Data & Text Mining.

SKILLS

Technical Skills: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Typescript, React JS, Next JS, Node JS, React Native, PostgreSQL, MySQL, GraphQL, RESTful API, Figma, UI/UX Design, Jest, Git (Version control), Storybook, Vercel. Tableu, Power BI.

Soft Skills: Communication, Collaboration, Problem Solver, Attention to Detail, Adaptability, Project Management.

Languages: Upper-Intermediate Proficiency in English, Fluency in Bahasa Indonesia.